

# Trịnh Vĩnh Trường

Developer

**Date of birth:** 22/05/1996

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 0384120066

Email: trinhvinhtruong@gmail.com

Address: K263 Trường Sơn, Hòa Thọ Tây, Cẩm Lệ, Đà Nẵng

Website: https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?

id=100005490255315

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Use my knowledge and skills to work with the team to develop products and also enhancing my experience. Learn new knowledge and technology in projects and from colleagues to improve my skills. Research work-related technologies to improve knowledge for working with current projects and future projects as well.

#### **EDUCATION**

9-2014 - 6-2019 Da Nang university of technology

Faculty: Electronics and Communication Engineering

Major: Computer science

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

09/2020 - Present FPT Software Company

- Read documents, perform tasks assigned by the leader.

- Join the meeting with the team, discuss to analyze requirements,

solve problems, report work.

09/2019 - 09/2020 Outfiz Company

- Read documents, perform tasks assigned by the leader.

- Research, propose solutions.

- Research technology applies to the project.

- Database research and design.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

2019 TOEIC Certificate with score 915 issued by IIG

#### **SKILLS**

**English** - Ability to listen, read and understand English documents well.

- Ability to communicate in English.

Programing - HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, C#

- Function-oriented programming, object-oriented programming

- Responsive and adaptive web design

- Working with ReactJS, VueJS, ASP.NET Core, jQuery, Bootstrap

Database	- MSSQL, MYSQL, POSGRESQL
Other technology	- Work with rabbitMQ - SVN, github

### **INTERESTS**

Badminton - Join the company's badminton activities every week. Soccer - Participate in the company's soccer football weekly. English - Join English club, English speaking cafe every week

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **RPA Botcare**

(05/2020 - Present)

Customer	D
Description	- Website to manage RPA bots, build functional modules to perform automation functions, automatically handle and notify operators when problems occurring
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Receive tasks from the leader, read documents and perform tasks</li> <li>Participating in the meeting to analyze requirements, build functionality</li> <li>Optimize code, optimize functions</li> <li>Bug fixing</li> </ul>
Technologies used	- VueJS, VueX, Vuetify, CSS

## **RPA Lifecycle Management**

(09/2020 - 05/2021)

Customer	
Description	- The website manages robotic process automation services, collects customer requirements, connects with RPA developers, manages execution costs, and works efficiently when using RPA. Manage RPA bots
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Receive tasks from the leader, read documents and perform tasks     Participating in the meeting to analyze requirements, build functionality     Optimize code, optimize functions     Bug fixing
Technologies used	- ReactJS, Redux, Redux-Saga, React Router, React Hooks, Material-UI, Formik, SCSS

### **Shop selling fashion clothes**

(2/2020 - 09/2020)

Customer	
Description	- Fashion sales website integrated with social networks
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	<ul> <li>Analysis and design of the module, write detailed design documents</li> <li>Module development</li> <li>Code optimization</li> <li>Bug fixing</li> </ul>

Technologies used	- ASP.NET Core, ReactJS, ReactNative - Microservices architecture - Restful API - Docker - Consul for managing service, Swagger for creating API document, Serilog for managing log, API version, Health check, RabbitMQ Client, Authentication Jwr Bearer, DDD architecture, MediatR, CQRS architecture, Dapper, Entity Framework, Repository, Unit of work, Autofac - Postgresql
-------------------	--

# Company Internal System (12/2019 - 2/2020)

Customer	
Description	- Website for management employee of the company
Team size	15
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Receive tasks from the leader, read documents and perform tasks - Error correction, code optimization
Technologies used	- Laravel, jquery - MVC architecture - MSSQL

# Company Internal System (9/2019 - 12/2019)

Customer	0
Description	- Website manages the database, automatically converts natural language to SQL statement, connects database with the website, and executes SQL.
Team size	8
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Receive tasks from the leader, read documents and perform tasks - Error correction, code optimization
Technologies used	- Laravel, jquery - MVC architecture - MSSQL